japanpropertycentral.com 2018-08-14

# Privacy Policy – JAPAN PROPERTY CENTRAL

## Who we are

Japan Property Central KK, Governor of Tokyo License No. (1) 96648, is a licensed real estate company located at Aoyama Palacio Tower 11F, 3-6-7 Kita Aoyama, Minato-ku, Tokyo, Japan. Our website address is http://japanpropertycentral.com.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Contact forms

We keep contact form submissions for a period of 7 years with a review every 3 years. You will have the opportunity to opt out or update or delete data at any point should you need to do so and details are set out in this policy as to how to do that. We do not use the information submitted through them for marketing purposes.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

We use Google Analytics to store information about how visitors use our website so that we may make improvements and give visitors a better user experience.

Google Analytics is a third-party information storage system that records information about the pages you visit, the length of time you were on specific pages and the website in general, how you arrived at the site and what you clicked on when you were there. These cookies do not store any personal information about you eg name, address etc and we do not share the data. You can view their privacy policy below:

Google – [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

## Who we share your data with

We do not share personal data collected through this website with any third party providers.

## How long we retain your data

We keep contact form submissions and privacy data records for a period of 7 years with a review every 3 years, and transaction records for 5 years. You will have the opportunity to opt out or update or delete data at any point should you need to do so and details are set out in this policy as to how to do that. We do not use the information submitted through them for marketing purposes.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Contact information

For privacy related inquiries, please contact us:

  * By email: info@japanpropertycentral.com
  * Or write to us at Japan Property Central KK, Aoyama Palacio Tower 11F, 3-6-7 Kita Aoyama, Minato-ku, Tokyo, Japan 107-0061

## Additional information

For the processing of personal data, we follow Japan’s privacy laws and require our clients to sign privacy agreements when using our services. For details, please refer to the signed Privacy Agreement.
